♪Mighty winds carry me to the heavens♪
♪On a wild steed,
I sing, smiling at the mortal world♪
♪Then the cold night veils the stars♪
♪I fall to the depths, yet walk alone♪
♪I brave countless snowy peaks♪
♪Your lingering warmth still fills
my palm♪
♪Though frost and snow may bar my way♪
♪The light in my eyes will never fade♪
♪With a sword that cleaves the clouds♪
♪With a heart as firm as stone♪
♪Through all I've endured,
I have no regrets♪
♪I'm still the boy I once was♪
=Sword God=
=Episode 1=
Elder Murong,
you've told us the names
of the ten ancient mythical beasts.
But if we were to rank them by strength,
(Wang Jie, Heavenly Sword Sect Disciple)
which one is the most powerful?
(Elder Murong, Heavenly Sword Sect)
The strongest and most troublesome
of them all has to be Bai Xi.
Bai Xi?
The legendary Bai Xi
who shares Goddess Nuwa's origin?
Yes.
She shares the same origin
as Goddess Nuwa,
with boundless demonic power.
Her cultivation is naturally formidable,
but she's brutal and quick-tempered.
She likes to eat humans.
The trickier part is that
most of the time
she disguises herself as a human.
She's nearly impossible to track.
No wonder the three Sword Immortals
had to join forces to slay her.
Too bad she managed to escape unscathed.
Then how can we tell
if Bai Xi has taken human form?
Her true form is over ten thousand feet long.
And she prefers to appear
as a beautiful woman.
Every time she transforms,
Bai Xi sheds her skin.
So there will be
lots of skin or scales left nearby.
(Zhao Feiyang, Heavenly Sword Sect)
Beautiful women,
troublesome...
Is there any way to counter her?
You're just a servant.
What right do you have to speak
at the sect assembly?
Learn some manners!
Exactly.
My... my apologies.
As for how to counter her,
Bai Xi has a serpent bloodline,
so realgar and strong liquor
have some effect on her.
Also:
Bai Xi enjoys drinking unrooted water,
namely rainwater
or dew.
Recent rumors say
she may very well be hiding
right here in Dongzhou.
So be careful
when you're out,
especially the male disciples.
Bai Xi likes to eat young men
rich in yang energy.
If some unknown beauty
throws herself at you,
be especially careful.
Thank you for your guidance,
Elder Murong!
Dismissed.
Can you believe it?
Three years ago,
he was our sect's chief disciple.
But his family was massacred,
and his fiancée took
his high-grade Dao Bone.
Now he's like a stray dog.
(The strongest and most troublesome)
(of them all has to be Bai Xi.)
(She prefers to appear
as a beautiful woman.)
(If some unknown beauty
throws herself at you,)
(be especially careful.)
Dear!
You're back.
Oh,
stop calling me that.
We're not officially married yet.
I insist.
You saved my life.
I have no way to repay you,
so I can only offer myself to you.
Or do you
find me repulsive
and want to abandon me?
No.
Of course not!
How could I ever abandon you?
That's good.
Dear, just wait.
I'll make you something delicious!
(Bai Xi enjoys drinking unrooted water,)
(namely rainwater)
(or dew.)
Bai!
Isn't...
Isn't that rainwater from last night?
You're drinking it just like that?
I love rainwater.
It comes from above. It's clean.
Dear,
I'm going to clean the room.
(Could she really be...)
(No way.)
(It can't be such a coincidence.)
(She's injured so badly.)
(Every time she transforms,)
(Bai Xi sheds her skin.)
(So there will be)
(lots of skin or scales left nearby.)
No wonder...
With my Dao Bone gone,
why would a woman like her
stay by my side?
(Bai Xi likes to eat young men
rich in yang energy.)
Is she going to eat me?
Why hasn't she made a move?
Blessing or curse,
I should ask her and find out.
Dear, what brings you here?
What's this?
Scales.
Where did they come from?
Dear,
you brought them here yourself,
and you're asking me?
(If I confront her now)
(and she attacks,)
(I won't make it out alive.)
(But I still have a blood feud
to settle.)
(I can't accept)
(dying like this.)
Dear,
what's wrong?
Are you feeling unwell?
No.
I'm not done sweeping yet.
Step out for a while.
Chen Qiushui?
What are you doing here?
(Chen Qiushui, Tianxuan Holy Maiden)
I'm going to the Heavenly Sword Sect
(Qingzhu, Holy Maiden's Maid)
tomorrow, so I thought I'd stop by.
You're not welcome here.
Get lost!
How dare you
show such disrespect to our Holy Maiden?
Zhao Feiyang!
I'm here to tell you:
I'm determined to claim
a divine-grade Dao Bone
from the Heavenly Sword Sect.
Then,
I'll return your high-grade Dao Bone
and give you some pills
to help you return to your peak.
Return it to me?
And give me pills?
What is this supposed to be?
Compensation?
You can see it that way.
Even if you win
that divine-grade Dao Bone,
my Dao Bone
is just worthless scrap
you've used and discarded.
Now you're giving me back
what you no longer want
and expect me to thank you?
Chen Qiushui,
you've really got this all figured out,
don't you?
You...
Zhao Feiyang,
I know I wronged you,
but I've never forgotten what we had.
Once I obtain the divine-grade Dao Bone,
besides returning your Dao Bone,
I'll also grant you a great opportunity.
Even more,
if you still wish to honor
our betrothal,
I won't refuse.
Our betrothal?
You still want to go through with it?
Yes.
There's so much
weighing on us.
Even so,
you'll always have a place
in my heart.
Dear?
Who is she?
Who are you?
Why are you touching my husband?
Zhao Feiyang,
you're married?
She's just...
Yes,
he's married.
Stop bothering him,
or else
I'll make you regret it!
Make us regret it?
What a bold claim!
A mere village woman
with no spiritual energy
dares to talk big
in front of our Holy Maiden?
You've got a death wish!
Zhao Feiyang,
tell me this isn't true!
It is.
She is my wife.
We've got nothing to talk about anymore.
And I will never forgive
what you've done.
Leave our home at once!
Very well.
Zhao Feiyang,
you'll regret this.
I'm sorry.
I was just...
It's okay, dear.
I'll go make dinner.
What's wrong, dear?
Who are you, really?
♪I once stood on high,
drawing spiritual energy into my blade♪
♪I laughed, pointing at the stars,
young and fearless♪
♪Then came my fall,
with frost and snow on my shoulders♪
♪My Dao foundation was damaged,
yet my Dao heart never wavered♪
♪I crossed countless peaks
to find my answer again♪
♪Through endless trials,
my Nascent Soul came♪
♪Heaven and earth my furnace,
I rose from the flame♪
♪No sword in hand,
yet numberless blades obey♪
♪I seek the Dao beyond the clouds♪
♪Unafraid of countless trials♪
♪With this flesh and soul♪
♪I shall forge a new age♪
♪Let thunder and fire crown me♪
♪Let wind and clouds heed me♪
♪At cultivation's peak♪
♪My first resolve remains unchanged♪
♪The sun and moon turn♪
♪I hear the Great Dao ring♪
♪I am the undying flame♪
♪Looking back when dust settles♪
♪At last I see, immortality♪
♪Lives in your smiles.♪